Contact

+48 514 768 681 mateusz.pyrka@gmail.com

Top Skills

JBoss / Wildfly Administration
Weblogic Administration
Software and hardware
Troubleshooting
Android and mobile technologies

Languages

English (Professional Working)
Polish (Native or Bilingual)

Education

Master's degree, IT and Technical Education

Mateusz Pyrka

Chief System Administrator in Information Technology Centre of the Department of Finance

Radom, Masovian District, Poland

Summary

Since 2011 I have been building experience in administration of application servers. I am responsible for maintaining JBoss, Weblogic, Oracle Application Server, Apache, Tomcat and Microsoft IIS servers on over 400 virtual machines. Privately, I'm interested in IoT, car mechanics, electronics and RPG games.

Certificates and courses

Certificate RHCJA - RedHat Certified JBoss Administrator Certificate ITIL v3 Foundation Certificate Prince2 Foundation

JB248- JBoss Application Administration I JB348-JBoss Application Administration II with exam

Oracle Weblogic Server 11g: Administration Essentials Ed 2 Oracle Weblogic Server 11g: Advanced Administration Ed 2 Oracle Weblogic Server 11g: Monitor and Tune Performance Oracle Database 11g: Administration Workshop Ed 2

Public Key Infrastructure (PKI)
Public Key Infrastructure (PKI) in Windows Server 2012, 2012 R2 i 2016

Apache Hadoop Administration

SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 11 SP2 Administration

Foglight software for databases Foglight software

Training in administration of HSM Thales nCipher modules - Cryptotech

Security clearance (confidential)

Experience

Chief System Administrator in Information Technology Centre of the Department of Finance

May 2011 - Present

- Daily administration of application servers Weblogic, JBoss, Oracle Application Server, Apache, Tomcat and IIS.
- Administration of HSM Thales servers,
- Support for the digital signature service system and PKI,
- Application server optimization, troubleshooting.
- Ensuring proper operating and technical conditions for business continuity
- Monitoring the status of the application environment and cooperation with other areas
- 3rd support line
- Participation in tender committees
- Participation in various projects

Event organization instructor In Municipal Cultural Center Amphitheater

June 2010 - May 2011

- Support for cultural events
- Recording of events organized by the Amphitheater
- Administer the resort website
- Editing photos and recorded recordings for the needs of the center's archive
- Support for stage equipment (sound system, lighting)
- Help in the implementation of audio concerts and events

Computer specialist In Ministry of Finance

April 2009 - June 2009

Apprenticeships in the IT Department of the Ministry of Finance of the Republic of Poland.

- Diagnosing hardware / software errors of workstations
- Configuring software and network devices
- Reinstallation of software and hardware
- 2nd support line for end users.

Projects

- HARF Computing cloud of the Ministry of Finance
- ePodatki Consolidation and centralization of customs and tax systems
- Construction of the e-Budget platform
- CVP Development of the catalog of public services of the National Tax Administration in the scope of digitizing taxpayer service and tax control suport
- PUESC Electronic Treasury and Customs Services Platform